>> 凯尔辛普森: 好的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right,
第三种方法是调用函数使用新关键字。
the third way that we'll look at
invoking functions uses the new keyword.
我完全理解新关键词好像有什么关系
And I fully understand that the new
keyword seems as if it has something to
与调用类构造函数一起使用。
do with invoking class constructors.
这与班级没有关系。
This has not got anything
to do with classes.
这只是一种不幸的语法
It's just an unfortunate syntactic
让它看起来像是在处理课的时候
trick to make it look like it's dealing
with classes when it really isn't.
实际上，新关键字是您可以调用函数的第三种方法。
Actually, the new keyword is the third
way that you can invoke a function.
结果证明它做了 4 件非常具体的事情
And it turns out that it does
four very specific things,
我要为你准备的名单
which I'm about to list for you.
它做了四个非常具体的事情
It does four very specific things,
当你看电话时就不太明显了
which are not particularly obvious
when you look at the call say.
但是新关键字的目的实际上是要调用
But the purpose of the new
keyword is actually to invoke
具有指向整个新空对象的此关键字的函数。
a function with a this keyword
pointing at a whole new empty object.
如果我们调用函数并将它们指向上下文对象，
If we have invoking functions and
pointing them at a context object,
就像个 workshop.ask ，那是一个方法。
like a workshop.ask, that's one way.
或者我们说我要调用一个函数并给它指定一个特定的对象。
Or we say I'm gonna invoke a function and
give it a specific object with .call or
.apply 或我将用一个 .bind 来强制它。
.apply or I'm gonna force it with a .bind.
第三种方法是说我想调用一个函数
A third way of doing it is to say
I wanna invoke a function and
使用全新的空对象。
use a whole new empty object.
新的关键词可以做到这一点。
And the new keyword can accomplish that.
它做其他事情但也完成了这一任务
It does other stuff, but
it also accomplishes that task,
即用新的空对象调用函数。
which is to invoke a function
with a new empty object.
现在我要说你可以实现同样的目标
Now, I would say that you could
accomplish that same goal
通过话，函数点调用，打开，闭合的大括号。
by saying, function dot call,
open, close curly bracket.
将在全新空对象的上下文中调用您的函数的 Cuz 。
Cuz that would invoke your function in
the context of a brand new empty object.
所以新的关键词并不是真正地向你买除了语法糖之外
So the new keyword isn't actually buying
you much except the syntactic sugar of,
我希望此函数使用新的此内容调用。
hey I want this function invoked
with a new this content.
这是我们第三次也是最后的方式。
That's our third and
final way of doing it.
那么这四件事情是怎样的呢 ?
So what are those four things by the way?
你要在这张幻灯片上再参考一下
You're gonna wanna be able to
refer back to this slide in a bit.
这个关键词的四个方面是什么，
What are the four things
that the this keyword,
当它用来调用我们的功能时，新关键字会做什么，我
that the new keyword is going to do when
it's used to invoke our function, what I
用重质空气加一个构造函数的话，这四个东西是什么 ?
call a with heavy air quotes a constructor
call, what are those four things?
数字 1，我们创建一个全新的空对象。
Number 1, number 1 we create
a brand new empty object.
我们已经知道了这部分但我们创造了一个全新的空物体
Well we already know that part but
we create a brand new empty object out
这就是新关键词所做的
of thin air,
that's what the new keyword does.
数字 2，新关键字将该对象链接到另一个对象。
Number 2, the new keyword links
that object to another object.
你在想什么呢
And you're thinking link, what?
这就是为什么那里有个星号
That's why there's an asterisk there.
我们会回来解释联系的
We'll come back and
explain the linkage later.
但它首先创建一个全新的对象，然后将它链接到某个地方。
But it first creates a brand new
object and then links it somewhere.
然后第三号调用函数
And then number 3,
it invokes the function,
它用它的，这个，关键字指向新对象来调用这个函数。
it calls the function with its, this,
keyword pointed at the new object.
不是链接对象，新对象。
Not the linked object, the new object.
>> Kyle Simpson: 第四，最后，函数调用后的新关键字
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And fourth and finally,
the new keyword after the function call is
完成，如果该函数不返回其自己的对象，
done, if that function does
not return its own object,
新关键字假定您打算返回此关键字。
the new keyword assumes that you
meant to return this keyword.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，这四种情况在每次出现新关键字时都发生
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So these four things
happen every single time a new keyword is
使用函数调用。
invoked with a function.
现在我只想从某种意义上说
Now I just wanna ask
sort of in a meta sense,
当我用这种方式描述的时候
which one, when I describe it this way,
这两个实体中的哪一个好像都在做呢 ?
which of the two entities seems
like it's doing all the work?
似乎新关键字正在执行所有工作，或者
Does it seem like the new keyword
is doing all the work, or
你的构造函数是否能完成所有工作
does it seem like your constructor
function's doing all the work?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这真的是新的关键词吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's really
the new keyword, isn't it?
事实上如果你在几乎所有功能上都有新的内容
As a matter of fact, if you put new
in front of almost any function,
即使是一个完全空的功能，所有四种情况都将发生。
even a completely empty function,
all four of these things would happen.
几乎就像功能根本不重要
It’s almost as if the function
doesn’t even matter.
新关键字只是把它的功能
The new keyword is just sort
of hijacking the function so
它能做到这四件事
that it can do these four things.